

Veysi ADIN

Date of birth: 17/02/1998

Nationality: Turkish

Gender: Male

CONTACT

Grönborgsgatan 13, 85233 Sundsvall, Sweden (Home)

veysi.adin@outlook.com

(+46) 0790660979

https://veysiadn.github.io/

https://www.linkedin.com/in/
veysiadn/

ABOUT ME

Hey! It's **Veysi ADIN**, **and** I'm a **Embedded System Engineer** located in Sundsvall, Sweden. I'm a Ph.D. student at Mid-Sweden University, and currently I'm working at Sensor Technology Research Center in Mid-Sweden University as a research assistant. I got my master's degeree in the field of robotics and control software development. I enjoy robotics, electronics, DIY projects and learning new things every day. I like to develop applications that solve real life problems.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/09/2022 - CURRENT - Sundsvall, Sweden

Research Assistant

Mid Sweden University

My research focuses on machine learning on embedded systems.

01/09/2020 - CURRENT - Seoul, South Korea

Research Assistant

Korea Institute of Science and Technology

I worked on development of control framework for medical robots, using EtherCAT protocol based on CiA402 standard and ROS2 as a middleware running on real-time Linux. As a use case for this control framework, we tested our framework on spine surgery robot being developed in Healthcare Robotics Center.

- I designed several PCBs, including safety watchdog PCB, and a flexible PCB for measuring force on the tip of attached instrument to spine surgery robot.
- Worked on safety and verification of medical robot and medical robot software complying various standards, including IEC62304, IEC60601-1/2, ISO 13485.

06/01/2020 - 31/08/2020 - Seoul, South Korea

R&D Intern

Korea Institute of Science and Technology

During this internship, I worked with a start-up company to implement control software and an initial prototype of a medical device called mic rodebrider, which is used in endoscopic sinus surgeries. Throughout this project, I used:

- · (++
- o Ot
- ∘ CiA402
- ∘ Git
- EPOS Linux Library
- Doxygen
- Raspberry Pi
- CAN Protocol
- EasyEDA (for custom PCB design)
- SolidWORKS (for prototype case design)

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/09/2022 - CURRENT - Sundsvall, Sweden

Electronics Ph.D.

Mid Sweden University

Address Sundsvall, Sweden | Website https://miun.se/

01/09/2020 - CURRENT - Seoul, South Korea

HCI & Robotics Master

University of Science and Technology / Korea Institute of Science and Technology

Address Seoul, South Korea | **Website** https://ust.ac.kr/eng.do | **Final grade** 4.33/4.5 | **Thesis** Deve lopment of Medical Device Control Software Framework

01/09/2015 - 24/05/2019 - Mersin, Turkey

Electrical & Electronics Engineer

Mersin University

Address Mersin, Turkey | **Final grade** 3.67/4 | **Thesis** Wi-Fi Controlled Natural Gas Valve System With Android Based Software

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Kurdish | Turkish

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening C2	Reading C2	Spoken production C2	Spoken interaction C2	Writing C2
Korean				
Listening B1	Reading B1	Spoken production B1	Spoken interaction B1	Writing A2

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

AI / Machine Learning / Deep Learning

Python / Tensorflow / PyTorch / ONNX & ONNX Runtime / Pandas Numpy Scikit-learn Scipy libraries **Embedded System Design**

C / ATMEL / STM32 / Altium Designer / Proteus / PCB Design

Software

MATLAB / C++ / Qt / Git / Julia / ROS/ROS2 / Real-time Linux

Prototyping Products

SolidWorks / SMD soldering / Arduino / Raspberry Pi

Others

LaTeX / EtherCAT / CiA 402 / Motion Control

CONFERENCES AND SEMINARS

> The 17th Asian Conference on Computer Aided Surgery / Virtual Conference

Development of Control Framework for Spine Surgery Robot Using EtherCAT

Abstract—As the more sensors and actuators are used in

the robotic systems to provide more features, complexity of the system is increasing. When it comes to medical robotics, it becomes harder to ensure safety and determinism in the system.

To deal with increasing complexity and ensure precise periodicity

and execution timing for a medical robot, in this paper we

report development of EtherCAT master as a part of software

framework for spine surgery robot. We implemented multi-axis

controller using open-source EtherCAT master running in realtime preemptive Linux.

We evaluated the real-time performance of the system in terms of periodicity, jitter and execution time in our first prototype of spine surgery robot.

https://github.com/veysiadn/veysiadn.github.io/raw/master/assets/pdf/ACCAS2021 VeysiADIN ChunwooKim.pdf

19/05/2021 – 21/05/2021 > – Seoul, South Korea / Korea Robotics Society

Development of motor control component for medical robot software framework based on EtherCAT

Component based software engineering principles can be applied to the development of a robot software to facilitate the complex development process. This paper reports development of a EtherCAT

master as part of a software framework for medical robot. A multi axis motor controller is implemented using

an open source EtherCAT master running in preemptive real-time Linux. The real-time performance of the

controller is evaluated in terms of periodicity, jitter, and execution time.

https://github.com/veysiadn/veysiadn.github.io/raw/master/assets/pdf/KROS Paper Veysi - Submitted 20210311.pdf

HONOURS AND AWARDS

24/05/2019

Valedictorian of Engineering Faculty – Mersin University Engineering Faculty I have ranked first among the faculty of engineering students graduating in 2019.

01/09/2016

Scholarship – Vehbi Koc Foundation

18/10/2021

Encouragement Award – Korea Institute of Science and Technology

KIST School organizes Idea Bubling Contents each year, where students implements their ideas related to industry, robotics and Al.

I attented the contest with my project called Portable-Progammable Real-time EtherCAT Master, and I won 3rd place among the 59 student projects.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UaHLfNDjBoc